After all, they are inferior Daoist sects from the mortal realm.
I've had enough playing with you.
Die.
Sister Gesang!
With this little skill,
you dare to run wild in Tushan.
Got it.
My blood.
How does it taste?
What's going on?
What did you do to me?
In my blood,
various spores are cultivated.
My blood.
are my weapons.
Right now, they
should be inside your body,
multiplying wildly.
You're bleeding a lot.
Let me bandage it for you.
Don't touch my blood.
So back then,
she didn't let me touch her blood
because of this.
I can't believe it's a brat like you.
I am a disciple of Qingxuan.
No one can kill me in Tushan.
Just you wait.
Sister Gesang.
Sister.
Don't come closer.
If you touch my blood,
I can't save you.
Sister Gesang.
But you're so badly injured.
What should we do?
Hurry and get some water.
Water, water, water.
Hurry.
Gods.
High Immortal.
How could this be?
If Qingxuan hadn't shown
the Hong Sword to the Heavenly Venerable,
the Heavenly Realm really wouldn't know
that you had secretly descended to the mortal realm.
Today, I've come specifically to apprehend you.
Do you plead guilty?
Guilty?
What crime have I committed?
Why is the Hong Sword
used to help people ascend,
while I am only used to punish immortals?
For tens of thousands of years,
how many immortal roots have I severed?
How much resentment have I absorbed?
I no longer want
to be that
ominous object feared by all.
High Immortal,
if you really want to take me away,
just kill me right here.
All things in the world
born between heaven and earth
merely have their own roles.
Whether ominous or not,
whether to kill you or not,
is not a choice for you or me.
Let's go.
The Heavenly Venerable will decide.
Yes.
Return Qingxuan's immortal root.
Qingxuan.
Greetings, High God.
How many years have you been cultivating?
Over a hundred years.
To have the opportunity to come to Sanshanliu
in just a short century,
it shows that you
are quite gifted.
Sanshanliu?
I am not talented.
I had an epiphany in Qingqiu,
and ascended here in a single thought.
I don't know
the name of this precious land.
In this world,
all those who cultivate immortality,
whether human
or demon,
if they have the chance to attain the Dao,
they will ascend here in their minds.
Through that Dharma gate,
they can reach the Nine Heavens
in the body of an immortal.
Thank you, High God.
But how
do I pass through this Dharma gate?
And where is
this Dharma gate?
Wait for me by the table under the tree.
Thank you, High God.
To understand the destiny
and know the nature.
Cultivation here,
when life ends,
all must enter reincarnation.
The heavenly dao
is also like this.
Drink this tea
to manifest your worldly emotions.
I will sever them with the Rainbow Sword.
Sever your thoughts
and leave them here.
Then you can pass through that gate with purity.
Thank you, High God.
But High God,
if my emotions are severed after drinking this tea...
Will the memories of the world
still exist?
Memories will not disappear.
It's just that your willpower
will become clearer and firmer.
Your perspective on all things
will be completely different from now.
Thank you for your guidance.
Thank you.
Go.
Cultivating as the Qingqiu Fox Clan
has blocked your true power, hasn't it?
I heard you possess extraordinary magic power.
But looking at it now,
it's nothing special.
Jinwang's demonic aura has disappeared.
Golden Immortal.
Just give in to me,
so you'll suffer less physical pain.
My Lady.
I beg you.
Save me.
Give me Chilan Bi'an.
What makes you think I will save you?
I have served you for centuries
with absolute loyalty.
Please.
Save me.
I will do anything for you from now on.
Thank you, My Lady.
My Lady,
what are you doing?
Didn't you promise to help me become an immortal?
Sorry you had to see that.
I'll ask you one last time.
Do you want to cultivate with me?
If I am to
lose my life here today,
it is my fate.
Sorry to trouble you.
Long time no see.
High God.
The High God delivering you with the Hong Sword
is his mercy.
Immortal root.
It is merely
the compassion of the primal energy attached to him.
Ping Jieqiang.